

NZ Permanent Resident



Auckland, NZ



+64 20 4117 8536



bertoni_elisa@hotmail.com







PROJECTS

<u>Devfolio</u> - a website showcasing all my past and ongoing projects.

MyLibrary - my first solo full-stack project, including unit tests covering over 80% of functions in the repo.

Gallerina - final Dev Academy group project. An art curation website that allows users to create their own collections of some of the most famous art pieces in the world. I developed the layout and features of the homepage and contributed to the styling of the entire website using Tailwind. I was also in charge of all PR and merges.

<u>K-ai-ndGPT</u> - a kind Chatbot developed using OpenAI API.



> TECH STACK

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- HTML
- CSS

- Express
- Knex
- Git

ELISA BERTONI

Junior Full Stack Developer



ABOUT ME

I am a full stack software developer with a background in customer service. My professional and personal interests have led me to enjoy a 10-year career in the hospitality industry in several countries around the world. Working closely with hospitality and stock management software has made me realise how much I love technology.

I have a keen eye for detail, strong organisational skills and impeccable customer service. Motivated and driven, I am now looking for my first role in the tech industry, and I believe my diverse experience and skill set make me a strong fit for your company.



EXPERIENCE

TRAINEE | DEV ACADEMY AOTEAROA

Remote, NZ

Jan 2023 - May 2023

An intensive 17-week web development training replicating real-life work environment by using agile methodologies.

The programme involved over 800 hours of hands-on coding where I learnt and became familiar with Git, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and TypeScript, React, Redux, Knex, TTD and unit testing, just to name a few.

The Bootcamp is packed with daily coding challenges, completed solo or in pairs, as well as weekly 24-hour group projects in teams of 4. The programme culminated with a five-day self-directed group project presented to a non-technical audience during graduation night.

Alongside tech concepts, there is also a huge emphasis on soft skills and we often discussed about empathy, self-compassion and wellbeing. I also opportunity to practice Nonviolent Communication, active listening, and providing and receiving growth feedback.

EDUCATION

AKKODIS ACCADEMY

10KWāhine Tech Talent Program: Microsoft Azure Training May 2023

DEV ACADEMY AOTEAROA

Certificate in Applied Software Development

Jan 2023 - May 2023

EIT HAWKE'S BAY

Diploma in Information Systems 2021-2022

UNIVERSITY OF MARBURG

Exchange - Erasmus Programme Feb 2012 - July 2012

UNIVERSITY OF MILAN

Bachelor's in Tourism, Geography and Environmental Sciences

2009-2013



LANGUAGES

Native Italian

Fluent English

Intermediate German



Outside of work I like cooking, eating good food and drinking fine wine.

I also love cycling, playing cards and jigsaw puzzles.

I am an eager traveler and you can often find me at the beach.

REFERENCES
AVAILABLE ON
REQUEST

ELISA BERTONI

Junior Full Stack Developer



EXPERIENCE

CELLAR DOOR DUTY MANAGER | PR WINEMAKERS NZ

Napier, NZ

Sep 2020 - Feb 2023

Overseeing the **day-to-day operations** of Church Road Cellar Door and supporting the team while they deliver premium tasting experiences and winery tours to visitors.

In-house **tech support** for the Cellar Door team, including troubleshooting till and eftpos-related issues and support staff with the company's cloud system, e.g. when encountering syncing issues.

Extensive use of ResDiary, SwiftPOS and EposNow.

TRAVEL AGENT | ANTIPODEAN LUXURY TRAVEL

Havelock North, NZ

Feb 2020 - Jun 2020

Organising bespoke travel itineraries and events for high-end clientele visiting New Zealand from overseas.

Even if for a short amount of time, this job gave me the opportunity to **hold courageous conversations**. A month into this position COVID-19 blew up and I had to face difficult conversations with not-so-pleasant customers wanting refunds on their prepaid upcoming trips.

Extensive use of HubSpot and Wetu.

RESTAURANT MANAGER | BISTRONOMY

Napier, NZ

Sep 2017 - Feb 2020

Leading and managing a team of 10-15 floor staff in a fast-paced 2 hats restaurant enabled me to practice leadership, resilience and working under pressure.

Stock and cash management helped me develop **strong organisation skills**.

Extensive use of Menumate(now POSbiz) and Eveve NZ.

Previous Overseas Experience Available on Request